GERARDUS SILVESTER SLEE

I am an architect, creative concluder, spatial prototypist, software developer, it consultant, musician, artist and teacher.

A multilingual architecture student of the university of cape town and the university of the free state from a Multicultural society with a vast skill set, and passion for all creative problem solving and design.

My last two years were dedicated to running a virtual reality start-up developing games and software for architects and engineers.

I love integrating new technologies and optimizing workflows and have an ability to inspire those around me. I am looking to work with people who want to drive change and alter the digital landscape.



49 Bellevue Street, Cape Town +2784 689 0159 gerard@slee.co.za

SKILL SET PC MAC REGINNER FAMILIAR PROFICIENT EXPERT MASTER UI DESIGN DESIGN WIREFRAMING ADOBE SUITE SPATIAL 3D MODELLING PHOTOGRAMMETRY RENDERING GAME ENGINES UNITY 3D Unreal Engine CODING LANGUAGES JS HLSL

. . . .

. . . .

00000

Management

Languages English

Afrikaans German

EMPLOYMENT

TENEBRIS LAB
2016 - CURRENT
FOUNDER, CEO AND BOARD MEMBER
DEVELOPED OUR OWN SOFTWARE FOR VIRTUAL AND AUGMENTED REALITY

IXPERIENCE [VR LECTURER] 2017 - CURRENT HEAD TEACHER FOR VR COURSE

SAOTA ARCHITECTS [ARCHITECT AND VR SPECIALIST] 2015 - 2016 HEADED UP THE VR DEPARTMENT AND INTEGRATED DIGITAL SOLUTIONS INTO THE WORKFLOWS OF ARCHITECTS

SLEE: SPATIAL PROTOTYPING AND VISUALISATION 2011-PRESENT PART-TIME SPATIAL PROTOTYPING AND CREATIVE CONSULTING

GMP-ARCHITEKTEN: BERLIN, DE [ARCHITECT AND LEAD ANIMATION ARTIST]
2011-2012
DESIGN, RAPID PROTOTYPING, FLY THROUGHS AND ANIMATIONS

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF THE FREE STATE
MASTERS OF ARCHITECTURAL STUDIES (PROFESSIONAL): 2014

UNIVERSITY OF THE FREE STATE BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL STUDIES HONOURS : 2013

UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN
BACHELOR OF ARCHITECTURAL STUDIES: 2008 - 2010

MICHAELHOUSE, HIGH SCHOOL HIGH SCHOOL: 2002 -2006

PROJECTS

2019 - ASTEROID MINDER - VR PROCEDURAL SPACE MINING GAME [Personal Project] https://youtu.be/TKsdLw3zL3s

2017 - LUX WALKER - INSTANT VR WALKTHROUGHS FOR ARCHITECTURE[LEAD DESIGN and CODE] www.luxwalker.com

2016- TENEBRIS GAME JAMS - IN HOUSE GAME JAMES TO CREATE VR INTERACTIONS [DIRECTOR + DEV] https://tenebrislab.com/games/

2015 - LIVE NORMAL - REAL TIME TEXTURING TOOL [Personal Project] https://tenebrislab.github.io/livenormal/

PUBLICATIONS

2014 - JOINT EXHIBITION AT OLIEWENHUIS ART MUSEUM, BLOEMFONTEIN -EXHIBITION OF ALL WORK DONE BY MARCH STUDENTS WITH DESTINCTIONS IN EITHER DESIGN, TECHNICAL RESOLUTION OR THEORETICAL DISCOURSE

2012 - DEZEEN | ARCHDAILY [SPORTS CONCERT COMPLEX, BAKU] [AVAILABLE: HTTP://GOO.GL/ZY7BS8]

- 8 MONTHS FROM DESIGN TO OPENING OF 20 000 SEATER CONCERT HALL.
- DESIGN TEAM, VISUAL SCHEDULING

2012 - ARTFLOW MAGAZINE [PERSONAL INTERVIEW] [AVAILABLE: HTTP://GOO.GL/X4OI2B]

AWARDS

2012 - ONCF MOROCCAN RAIL COMPETITION GMP ARCHITECTS [RUNNER UP]

2011 - TWINMOTION VISUALISATION AWARD

2010 - DES BAKER ARCHITECTURAL AWARD [SECOND RUNNER UP]

PERSONAL INTERESTS

I have been heavily focused on Virtual Reality and Augmented Reality using any tools and languages available to me. I love exploring new technologies. I am constantly creating prototypes of ideas and integrating API's in creative ways.

My Architecture background means that I have an ability to take concepts through to completed products using a design orientated approach. I am very fluent in c# and uxdesign as well as management of a team. Being a board member and founder of my start up means I know how to deal with stress and how to translate instructions and progress between all parties involved with a business

I have taken concepts from design phase through deployment on multiple platforms.

I am an early adopter of technology and love to explore software development, constantly on the hunt for new tools and Human Interface devices that bridge the gap between design and technology.